Muhammad Imanullah Front-End Developer

Gresik, Indonesia | 081333964928 | mimanullah26@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github | Web

SUMMARY

A Front End Developer who has been working for over 3 years, has expertise in Vue.js, React.js, Nuxt.js, Next.js, Laravel, and Nest.js. During the development process, the languages often used include Javascript, Typescript, and PHP. I focused on learning JavaScript ES6, Typescript, and frameworks related to using JavaScript. I am also interested in mobile development using Dart language and Flutter Framework, and backend development using Nodejs and Nest Framework.

EXPERIENCE

Generasih GIGI 3.0 Full Stack Engineer – Indonesia

GoTo Impact Foundation - Apprenticeship (Jun 2023 - Present)

- Currently enrolled in the Full Stack Engineer program at GIGIH, collaborating with industry leaders to gain expertise in cloud technologies and enhance problem-solving skills.
- Learning about MERN(MongoDB, Express, React.js, Node.js) technology.

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka – Indonesia Cloud Computing Student - Apprenticeship (Feb 2023 – Jul 2023)

- Currently enrolled in the Cloud Computing program at Bangkit Academy, collaborating with industry leaders to gain expertise in cloud technologies and enhance problem-solving skills.
- Working with Amati Indonesia Company on developing the learning path for the Greenskill Education Platform using Nest.js for backend and Next.js for frontend.

PT. LOGIQUE DIGITAL INDONESIA – Jakarta, Indonesia

Vuejs Developer - Full-time (Nov 2022 – Apr 2023)

- Work with the UI/UX Designer, Back-end, and QA Engineer to create applications.
- Developed backoffice web applications using Vue 3 with typescript.

PT Roketin - Bandung, Indonesia

Front-end Developer - Full-time (Mei 2022 - Nov 2022)

- Work with the UI/UX Designer, Back-end, and QA Engineer to create applications.
- Developed backoffice web applications using Nuxt.js.

PT DOT Indonesia – Malang, Indonesia

Front-end Developer - Full-time (Aug 2019 - Jan 2022)

- Work with the UI/UX Designer, Back-end, and QA Engineer to create applications.
- Implement CSS using a tailwind or bootstrap framework based on designs created in Figma.
- Proficient in multiple languages, frameworks, and content management systems including JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Vue, Nextjs, Nuxtjs, and Inertia, among others.

PT Kelola Mina Laut - Gresik, Indonesia

Information Technology Support Engineer - Intern (Jul 2018 – Sep 2018)

- Manage backoffice application PT. Kelola Mina Laut with Laravel
- Build a mobile app for approving fish shipments with Android Java

EDUCATION

STATE UNIVERSITY OF MALANG (2020 - PRESENT)

S1 Information Engineer

VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL TELKOM MALANG (2017 - 2019)

Software Engineering

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, SASS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- PHP
- JavaPython
- Node.jsVue, Vue3, Nuxt.jsReact, Next.js
- Nest.jsLaravel